Guide to the Rice University Football programs collection, 1913-2018 UA 223
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
Rice University Football programs collection
1913-2018
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas https://library.rice.edu/woodson
Rice University.
UA 223
8.25 Linear Feet (17 boxes)
This collection contains programs from football games.
Biographical Sketch
The programs trace the history of Rice University football from its inception until the present.
Scope and Contents
The programs include the names of the opposing institutions, dates of the games, pictures and background of the players
Access Restrictions
This material is open for research
Conditions Governing Access
Stored off-site at the Library Service Center. Please request this material via woodson@rice.edu or call 713-348-2586.
Acquisition Information
Transferred from the Rice University Athletic Department.
Index Terms
Subjects
Universities and colleges; Football; College sports; Sports
Document Types
programs (documents)
- Series I: 1913-1969, 231673
  - Rice vs. Southwestern University (3 copies), November 18, 1913; 231886 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, November 9, 1914; 231885 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - University of Arizona vs. Rice, November 30, 1916; 231884 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 27, 1917; 231883 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice (2 copies), November 29, 1917; 231882 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 21, 1921; 231881 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Oklahoma University (2 copies), November 21, 1921; 231880 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Rice vs. Texas (2 copies), November 4, 1922; 231879 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas University, November 11, 1922; 231878 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M (2 copies), November 14, 1925; 231877 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, 1927 (month/day not shown); 231876 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Sewanee vs. Rice, November 1, 1930; 231875 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - TCU vs. Rice, November 8, 1930; 231874 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - LSU vs. Rice, October 1, 1932; 231873 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Loyola vs. Rice, October 15, 1932; 231872 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Loyola vs. Rice, October 7, 1933; 231871 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - SMU vs. Rice, October 14, 1933; 231870 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 28, 1933; 231869 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Santa Clara, November 4, 1933; 231868 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, November 11, 1933; 231867 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Purdue vs. Rice, October 6, 1934; 231866 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Texas vs. Rice (2 copies), October 27, 1934; 231865 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - University of Arkansas vs. Rice, November 10, 1934; 231864 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - TCU vs. Rice, November 24, 1934; 231863 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, 1934 (month/day not shown); 231862 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Duquesne vs. Rice (2 copies), October 5, 1935; 231861 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Rice vs. Creighton (2 copies), October 12, 1935; 231860 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Rice vs. George Washington, November 2, 1935; 231859 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, 231858 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Rice vs. Texas, November 16, 1935; 231857 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 30, 1935; 231856 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, October 10, 1936; 231855 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 24, 1936; 231854 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Rice vs. George Washington, October 31, 1936; 231853 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Rice vs. TCU (2 copies), November 21, 1936; 231852 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 28, 1936; 231851 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Rice vs. SMU, December 5, 1936; 231850 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Rice vs. LSU, October 9, 1937; 231849 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. Tulsa University, October 16, 1937; 231848 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Rice vs. Auburn, October 30, 1937; 231847 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 6, 1937; 231846 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M (2 copies), November 13, 1937; 231845 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 27, 1937; 231844 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Colorado (2 copies), January 1, 1938; 231843; Cotton Bowl (copies have different cover art) (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Oklahoma vs. Rice, October 1, 1938; 231842 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 22, 1938; 231841 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Auburn vs. Rice, October 29, 1938; 231840 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - TCU vs. Rice (2 copies), November 19, 1938; 231839 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Baylor vs. Rice, November 26, 1938; 231838 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - SMU vs. Rice, December 3, 1938; 231837 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Vanderbilt vs. Rice, September 30, 1939; 231836 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. Centenary, October 7, 1939; 231835 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Rice vs. Sam Houston, October 21, 1939; 231834 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 1, 1939; 231833 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 15, 1939; 231832 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, December 2, 1939; 231831 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Centenary vs. Rice, October 5, 1940; 231830 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - LSU vs. Rice, October 12, 1940; 231829 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, October 19, 1940; 231828 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 26, 1940; 231827 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - SMU vs. Rice, December 7, 1940; 231826 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Sam Houston vs. Rice, October 4, 1941; 231825 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Tulane vs. Rice, October 11, 1941; 231824 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 25, 1941; 231823 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Centenary vs. Rice, November 1, 1941; 231822 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, November 8, 1941; 231821 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, November 15, 1941; 231820 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - TCU vs. Texas, November 15, 1941; 231819 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Baylor vs. Rice, November 29, 1941; 231818 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - LSU vs. Rice, October 3, 1942; 231817 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 24, 1942; 231816 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Texas Tech vs. Rice, October 31, 1942; 231815 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, November 14, 1942; 231814 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - TCU vs. Rice, November 21, 1942; 231813 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Tulane vs. Rice, October 9, 1943; 231812 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Galveston Army Airfield vs. Rice, September 23, 1944; 231811 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Randolph Field vs. Rice, September 30, 1944; 231810 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - SMU vs. Rice, October 21, 1944; 231809 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 28, 1944; 231808 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Texas Tech vs. Rice, November 4, 1944; 231807 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, November 18, 1944; 231806 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Southwestern vs. Rice, December 2, 1944; 231805 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Southwestern vs. Rice (2 copies), October 6, 1945; 231804 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Tulane vs. Rice (2 copies), October 13, 1945; 231803 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Texas Tech vs. Rice, November 3, 1945; 231802 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, November 10, 1945; 231801 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, November 17, 1945; 231800 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Southwestern vs. Rice, October 6, 1946; 231799 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - SMU vs. Rice, October 19, 1946; 231798 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 26, 1946; 231797 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Texas Tech vs. Rice, November 2, 1946; 231796 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - TCU vs. Rice, November 23, 1946; 231795 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Orange Bowl - Tennessee vs. Rice, January 1, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - USC vs. Rice, October 4, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Tulane v. Rice, October 11, 1947 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - LSU vs. Rice, October 2, 1948; 231794 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - SMU vs. Rice, October 16, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 23, 1948; 231793 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Baylor vs. Rice, November 27, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Clemson vs. Rice, September 24, 1949; 231792 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - New Mexico vs. Rice, October 8, 1949; 231791 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 22, 1949; 231790 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Texas Tech vs. Rice, October 29, 1949; 231789 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, November 5, 1949; 231788 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, November 12, 1949; 231787 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Baylor vs. Rice (2 copies, different covers), November 26, 1949; 231786; Copies have different cover art (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - North Carolina vs. Rice (Cotton Bowl), January 2, 1950; 231785 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Rice vs. Santa Clara, September 30, 1950; 231784 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Rice vs. LSU, October 7, 1950; 231783 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Pitt vs. Rice, October 14, 1950; 231782 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 21, 1950; 231781 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 28, 1950; 231780 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, November 4, 1950; 231779 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 25, 1950; 231778 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Baylor vs. Rice, December 2, 1950; 231777 (Box 3a, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. Clemson, September 29, 1951; 231776 (Box 3a, Folder 2)
  - Rice vs. Navy, October 13, 1951; 231775 (Box 3a, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 21, 1951; 231774 (Box 3a, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. Pittsburgh, November 3, 1951; 231773 (Box 3a, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 10, 1951; 231772 (Box 3a, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 17, 1951; 231771 (Box 3a, Folder 7)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, December 1, 1951; 231770 (Box 3a, Folder 8)
  - Rice vs. LSU, October 4, 1952; 231769 (Box 3a, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 25, 1952; 231768 (Box 3a, Folder 10)
  - Rice vs. Wisconsin, November 1, 1952 (Box 3a, Folder 11)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 22, 1952; 231767 (Box 3a, Folder 12)
  - Rice vs. Florida, September 19, 1953; 231766 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. Cornell, October 3, 1953; 231765 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Rice vs. Hardin-Simmons, October 10, 1953; 231764 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. SMU (Cotton Bowl), October 17, 1953; 231763 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 24, 1953; 231762 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. Kentucky, October 31, 1953; 231761 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 7, 1953; 231760 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 14, 1953; 231759 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 21, 1953; 231758 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 28, 1953; 231757 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Alabama vs. Rice (Cotton Bowl), January 1, 1954; 231756 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Rice vs. Florida, September 18, 1954; 231755 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Rice vs. Cornell, October 2, 1954; 231754 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 16, 1954; 231753 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 23, 1954; 231752 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Rice vs. Vanderbilt, October 30, 1954; 231751 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, November 13, 1954; 231750 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 20, 1954; 231749 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Clemson, October 8, 1955; 231748 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 12, 1955; 231747 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Rice vs. Alabama, September 22, 1956; 231746 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Rice vs. LSU, October 6, 1956; 231745 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 27, 1956; 231744 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Rice vs. Utah, November 3, 1956; 231743 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 24, 1956; 231742 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Rice vs. Duke, October 12, 1957; 231741 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Rice vs. Clemson, November 2, 1957; 231740 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 16, 1957; 231739 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Rice vs. Navy (Cotton Bowl), January 1, 1958; 231738 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Rice vs. LSU, September 20, 1958; 231737 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 25, 1958; 231736 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Rice vs. Army, November 8, 1958; 231735 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 15, 1958; 231734 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Rice vs. Florida, October 10, 1959; 231733 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 17, 1959; 231732 (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Rice vs. Clemson, October 31, 1959; 231731 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 7, 1959; 231730 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 14, 1959; 231729 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 28, 1959; 231728 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, October 1, 1960; 231727 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Rice vs. Florida, October 8, 1960; 231726 (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 22, 1960; 231725 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 12, 1960; 231724 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 19, 1960; 231723 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Ole Miss vs. Rice (Sugar Bowl), January 2, 1961; 231722 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. LSU, September 23, 1961; 231721 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Georgia Tech vs. Rice, September 30, 1961; 231720 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 21, 1961; 231719 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 28, 1961; 231718 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 11, 1961; 231717 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, December 2, 1961; 231716 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Rice vs. Penn State, October 6, 1962; 231715 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Rice vs. Oregon, October 13, 1962; 231714 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 27, 1962; 231713 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, November 3, 1962; 231712 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Rice vs. Stanford, October 12, 1963; 231711 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 19, 1963; 231710 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 26, 1963; 231709 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 9, 1963; 231708 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 16, 1963; 231707 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 30, 1963; 231706 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. LSU, 1964-09-26 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 24, 1964; 231705 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, October 31, 1964; 231704 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 14, 1964; 231703 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 21, 1964; 231702 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Rice vs. LA Tech, 1965-09-18 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - LSU vs. Rice, 1965-09-25 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 16, 1965; 231701 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 23, 1965; 231700 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, 1965-11-06 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - TCU vs. Rice, November 20, 1965; 231699 (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Rice vs. LSU, September 24, 1966; 231698 (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Tennessee vs. Rice, 1966-10-01 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Rice vs. UCLA, October 8, 1966; 231697 (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Rice vs. SMU, 1966-10-15 (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 22, 1966; 231696 (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, October 29, 1966; 231695 (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, 1966-11-05 (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 12, 1966; 231694 (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 19, 1966; 231693 (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Baylor vs. Rice, 1966-11-16 (Box 5, Folder 38)
  - LSU vs. Rice, September 23, 1967; 231692 (Box 5, Folder 39)
  - Rice vs. Navy, September 30, 1967; 231691 (Box 5, Folder 40)
  - Rice vs. Northwestern, October 14, 1967; 231690 (Box 5, Folder 41)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 21, 1967; 231689 (Box 5, Folder 42)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 28, 1967; 231688 (Box 5, Folder 43)
  - Texas Tech vs. Rice, 1967-11-04 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 11, 1967; 231687 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 18, 1967; 231686 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - TCU vs. Rice, 1967-11-25 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, December 2, 1967; 231685 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. LSU, September 28, 1968; 231684 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Tennessee, October 5, 1968; 231683 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 26, 1968; 231682 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, November 2, 1968; 231681 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 23, 1968; 231680 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Rice vs. Virginia Military Institute, September 20, 1969; 231679 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Rice vs. LSU, September 27, 1969; 231678 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 18, 1969; 231677 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 8, 1969; 231676 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 15, 1969; 231675 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 29, 1969; 231674 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Series II: 1970-2011, 231474
  - Rice vs. Virginia Military Institute, September 19, 1970; 231672 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. California, October 3, 1970; 231671 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 24, 1970; 231670 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, October 31, 1970; 231669 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 21, 1970; 231668 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Rice vs. University of Houston, September 11, 1971; 231667 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Rice vs. USC, September 18, 1971; 231666 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, September 25, 1971; 231665 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 16, 1971; 231664 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 23, 1971; 231663 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 6, 1971; 231662 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 13, 1971; 231661 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 27, 1971; 231660 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Rice vs. University of Houston, September 9, 1972; 231659 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Rice vs. Clemson, September 23, 1972; 231658 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Rice vs. Louisiana State, October 7, 1972; 231657 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 28, 1972; 231656 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, November 4, 1972; 231655 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 25, 1972; 231654 (Box 6, Folder 35)
  - University of Houston vs. Rice, September 15, 1973; 231653 (Box 6, Folder 36)
  - Rice vs. Montana, September 22, 1973; 231652 (Box 6, Folder 37)
  - Rice vs. Notre Dame, October 13, 1973; 231651 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 20, 1973; 231650 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 27, 1973; 231649 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 10, 1973; 231648 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 17, 1973; 231647 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, December 1, 1973; 231646 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. University of Houston, September 14, 1974; 231645 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Cincinnati, September 24, 1974; 231644 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Rice vs. LSU, September 28, 1974; 231643 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 26, 1974; 231642 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, November 2, 1974; 231641 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, November 9, 1974; 231640 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Rice vs. TCU, November 23, 1974; 231639 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Rice vs. Vanderbilt, September 20, 1975; 231638 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Rice vs. Mississippi State, October 11, 1975; 231637 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. SMU, October 18, 1975; 231636 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 8, 1975; 231635 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, November 15, 1975; 231634 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 29, 1975; 231633 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Utah, September 18, 1976; 231632 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 2, 1976; 231631 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, October 16, 1976; 231630 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, October 23, 1976; 231629 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Rice vs. SMU, November 6, 1976; 231628 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 13, 1976; 231627 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Rice vs. Idaho, September 10, 1977; 231626 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. Florida, September 17, 1977; 231625 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - LSU vs. Rice, September 24, 1977; 231624 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Texas vs. Rice, October 1, 1977; 231623 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. TCU, October 8, 1977; 231622 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, October 22, 1977; 231621 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, October 29, 1977; 231620 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - SMU vs. Rice (Cotton Bowl), November 5, 1977; 231619 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Baylor vs. Rice, November 12, 1977; 231618 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. University of Houston, November 26, 1977; 231617 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Rice vs. Iowa State, September 9, 1978; 231616 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Rice vs. Texas, September 16, 1978; 231615 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Rice vs. LSU, September 30, 1978; 231614 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - TCU vs. Rice, October 14, 1978; 231613 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 21, 1978; 231612 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, October 28, 1978; 231611 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, November 4, 1978; 231610 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. SMU, November 11, 1978; 231609 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 18, 1978; 231608 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - University of Houston vs. Rice, Decemebr 2, 1978; 231607 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, September 15, 1979; 231606 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Rice vs. Oklahoma, September 29, 1979; 231605 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Rice vs. TCU, October 13, 1979; 231604 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Texas Tech vs. Rice, October 20, 1979; 231603 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, October 27, 1979; 231602 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, November 3, 1979; 231601 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Rice vs. University of Houston, December 1, 1979; 231600 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Clemson vs. Rice, September 13, 1980; 231599 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Tulane vs. Rice, September 20, 1980; 231598 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Rice vs. LSU, September 27, 1980; 231597 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Rice vs. Texas, October 4, 1980; 231596 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - TCU vs. Rice, October 11, 1980; 231595 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, October 18, 1980; 231594 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Texas A&M vs. Rice, October 25, 1980; 231593 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, November 1, 1980; 231592 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Rice vs. SMU, November 8, 1980; 231591 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 15, 1980; 231590 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - University of Houston vs. Rice, November 29, 1980; 231589 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Texas vs. Rice, September 12, 1981; 231588 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Missouri vs. Rice, September 19, 1981; 231587 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - LSU vs. Rice, September 26, 1981; 231586 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Rice vs. Tulane, October 3, 1981; 231585 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. TCU, October 10, 1981; 231584 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Texas Tech vs. Rice, October 17, 1981; 231583 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, October 24, 1981; 231582 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Rice vs. Arkansas, October 31, 1981; 231581 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - SMU vs. Rice, November 7, 1981; 231580 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Baylor vs. Rice, November 14, 1981; 231579 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Rice vs. University of Houston, November 28, 1981; 231578 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Rice vs. SW Lousiana, September 11, 1982; 231577 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Tulane vs. Rice, September 18, 1982; 231576 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - LSU vs. Rice, September 25, 1982; 231575 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - TCU vs. Rice, October 9, 1982; 231574 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Rice vs. Texas Tech, October 16, 1982; 231573 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Arkansas vs. Rice, October 30, 1982; 231572 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Rice vs. SMU, November 6, 1982; 231571 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Rice vs. Baylor, November 13, 1982; 231570 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - University of Houston vs. Baylor, November 27, 1982; 231569 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Rice vs. University of Houston, September 1, 1983; 231568 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Rice vs. Minnesota, September 10, 1983; 231567 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Rice vs. LSU, September 17, 1983; 231566 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Rice vs. SW Louisiana, September 24, 1983; 231565 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Rice vs. TCU, October 8, 1983; 231564 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Texas Tech vs. Rice, October 15, 1983; 231563 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Rice vs. Texas A&M, October 22, 1983; 231562 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Baylor vs. Rice, November 12, 1983; 231561 (Box 10, Folder 16)